<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Career_guru</string>
    <string name="navi_drawer_open">open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navi_drawer_close">close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="textview">The subjects covered in a diploma in mechanical engineering program typically include a combination of core and elective topics, providing students with a strong foundation in both theoretical and practical aspects of the field.\nSome of the common subjects found in the curriculum of a diploma in mechanical engineering are:\nEngineering Mathematics,Engineering Physics,Engineering Chemistry,Environmental Studies,Engineering Mechanics,Electrical Technology,Computer Fundamentals,Thermodynamics,Fluid Mechanics,Manufacturing Processes,Machine Design,Control Systems,CAD/CAM,Project Management,Hydraulics,Applied Physics,Applied Chemistry,Strength of Materials,Power Plant Engineering,Non-Conventional Energy Resources,Metal Casting Science and Engineering."
    </string>


    <string name="textscience">
        <br>There are two sub-branches in the Science stream, divided based on the third subject you study:\n</br>
        <br>Medical: This branch includes Physics, Chemistry, Biology, and English, along with an optional subject.\n</br>
        <br>Non-Medical: This branch includes Physics, Chemistry, and Mathematics, along with an optional subject.</br>


    </string>

    The science stream is a popular choice for students who are interested in pursuing careers in
    fields such as medicine, research, or technology.The subjects in the science stream in class 11
    include Physics, Chemistry, Biology, Mathematics, and Computer Science Physics and Chemistry are
    common to both the Non-medical and Medical stream, while Mathematics is taken by students who
    wish to pursue careers in engineering, architecture, aeronautics, etc. Biology is chosen if one
    wants to start a career in the medical field The science stream offers an enticing path of
    exploration and discovery, unveiling the intricacies of the natural world and the human body. It
    fuels curiosity, challenges the intellect, and inspires innovation. By pursuing the science
    stream, students embark on a thrilling adventure where they become detectives, unraveling the
    mysteries of atoms, life, and the cosmosAfter completing the science stream, students can pursue
    various career paths such as engineering, medicine, research and development, data analysis, and
    scientific writing


</resources>